President's Office Records, 1927-1981
University of Houston Libraries
- Subject Files (Box 1-50)
  - Johnson Space Center, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Jesse Jones Interests, 1947-1962 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Jones Scholarships - General, 1948-1949 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Jones Scholarships - General, 1951-1958 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Jones Scholarships - Jesse H. (Technology), 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Jones Scholarships - Mary Gibbs and Jeannette, 1948-1949 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Jones Scholarships - Mary Gibbs and Jeannette, 1949-1957 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Jones Scholarships - Reports and Agreements, 1948-1950 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Jones Scholarships - Reports and Agreements, 1951-1958 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Junior College - Committee to Study, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Junior College Conference, 1967-1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Junior Colleges, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Kennedy, John F., Memorial Services, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Kenneth Franzheim Memorial Library in Architecture, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - KHOU-TV, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - KUHT-TV, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - KUHT-TV, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - KUHT-TV, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - KUHT TV Accounting Statements, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - KUHT General, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - KUHT General, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Land Purchases (Box 30-31)
    - M.D. Anderson and H.R. Cullen, 1943-1947 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Myer Tract, Wheeler and Calhoun, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Settegast Park, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Settegast Tract, 1936-1938 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Settegast Tract, 1942-1952 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Taub Tract and Taub Deed, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Taub Tract and Taub Deed, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - University Campus, 1945-1964 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - West Side of Calhoun, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - West Side of Calhoun, 1937-1938 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - West Side of Calhoun, 1942-1944 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - West Side of Calhoun, 1945-1951 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Wunderlich Tract, 1944-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Land Sale Malone House, 1956-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Land Sale of 2 acres to Catholic Church, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Land Sale of .235 acres to Mrs. Louise Mueller, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Latin American Studies Association, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Latin American Symposium, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Law, Bates College of, Dedication, 1969-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Law, College of, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Law, College of, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Law, College of, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Law, College of, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Law, College of, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Law, College of, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Law, College of, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Law, College of, Foundation, 1952-1960 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Law Fraternity (Delta Theta Phi), 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Law - J. D. Degree, 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Law - National College of District Attorneys, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Law School - re: Merger of South Texas, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - LeBlanc, Lewis, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Legal Center, Houston, 1961-1965 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Legal Status - University of Houston, 1941-1956 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Acts Pertaining to the University of Houston, Junior College, etc., 1927-1959 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Act - Proposing Full State Support, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Bills - 63rd Legislature, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Bills - 63rd Legislature, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Budget Board, 1962-1973 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Budget Board, 1973-1977 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Budget Board, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Budget Board, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Dinner Party, 1957-1960 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Dinner Party, December 17, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Luncheon, December 5, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Legislators, Harris County Delegation, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Legislators-Harris County Delegation, 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Legislators Luncheon, Dec. 17, 1968, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Legislators - Party, June 7, 1961, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Legislators, Texas, 1968-1973 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Legislators, Texas, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
  - Legislators-Texas (other than Harris County), 1974-1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Legislature, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Legislature, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Legislature, 65th (1977), 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10-11)
  - Library (Box 32-33)
    - Bates Texana and Western Americana, 1964-1969 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Bates, W.B. Texana and Western Americana, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Broadman, 1947-1954 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Burgess, 1948-1952 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Collections (Jack Wilson), 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Dedication, 1950-1951 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Dedication of Freeman Wing, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - General, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - General, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - General, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - General, 1973-1976 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - General, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - International, 1954-1956 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - James F. Lincoln Arc Welding, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Joseph W. Evans Memorial Bibliography Collection, 1964-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Max Freund Collection, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Max Westheimer Memorial, 1946-1950 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Maverick, Maury, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Michaelis Collection, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Miller, E. E. (Library), 1951-1954 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - South America, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Spanish Collection, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Ziegler Collection, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Limits to Growth, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
  - Living Endowment Association, 1958-1964 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, 1963-1971 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Louisiana State University, 1959-1975 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Loyalty Oath, 1947-1967 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Lunar Receiving Laboratory, 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Lunar Sciences Institute, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Mace, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Mail Service, 1956-1979 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Management, Department of, 1955-1968 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Management Development Center, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Management Development Center, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Marcus, Stanley, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Marine Biomedical Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Marshall, Douglas B., 1951-1957 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - McCary, Dr. James L.-Psychology, 1964-1974 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - McElhinney Hall Dedication, 1965-1974 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - McGraw-Hill, 1956-1973 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - M.D. Anderson Chairs, 1956-1971 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - M.D. Anderson Foundation Chairs, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - M.D. Anderson Foundation, Endowment Fund, 1946-1961 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - M.D. Anderson Foundation, Endowment Fund, 1962-1969 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - M.D. Anderson Foundation, Endowment Fund, 1971-1975 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 1962-1974 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Melcher, Leroy, Sr., 1968-1972 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Merritt, Mrs. Curtis H., 1971-1977 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Military Duty-Student, 1962-1968 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Military Science, Department of, 1970-1974 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Mills, Mabel, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Minnie Stevens Piper Foundation, 1961-1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Minnie Stevens Piper Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Mission Self-Study, (General), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Grant, 1948-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Monsignor John T. Nicholson Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Monterrey, Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores, 1950-1957 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Montz, Ted, Facilities Planning and Construction (Box 34, Folder 9-19)
    - Director of, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Director of, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
    - Vice-President, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
    - Vice-President, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Vice-President, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
    - Project Status Report, June 1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Project Status Report, September 1979 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Project Status Report, December 1979 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Moody Foundation, 1955-1965 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Moody Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Moody Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Moody Foundation, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Moody Towers Dedication, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Munitz, Barry, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Music, School of, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Music, School of, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1960-1973 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 35, Folder 5-12)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - General, 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Work - Inter-institutional, 1963-1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Manned Spacecraft Center Graduate Education Center, 1965-1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Relation, Committee on, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rental of Old KTRK Building, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Research Grants (Office of the President), 1962-1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Research Grants (Office of Research), 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1969 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - National Association of College and University Attorneys, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 16-19)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 20-22)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-grant State Colleges, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - National College Athletics Association (NCAA) (Box 35-36)
    - NCAA General, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - NCAA General, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - NCAA General, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - re: NCAA Probation, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - re: NCAA Probation, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - re: NCAA Probation, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - re: NCAA Probation, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - National Defense Education Act (NDEA), 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - National Defense Grants, 1958-1964 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1958-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 1952-1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - National Space Institute, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - National Student Association, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Natural Sciences and Mathematics, College of (Box 36, Folder 17-20)
    - Biophysical Science, Department of, 1971-1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Chemistry, Department of, 1974-1979 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Geology, Department of, 1974-1979 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Mathematics, Department of, 1968-1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Naval Reserve Armory, 1947-1964 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1960-1973 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - North Campus, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - North Campus, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - North Campus, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 25-26)
  - North Carolina, University of, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Nursery School, 1951-1970 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Nursing, 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Nursing, Central College of, Discontinuation of, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Nursing, Central College of, Discontinuation of, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Nursing, Central College of, Discontinuation of, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Nursing, Central College of, Discontinuation of, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1975-1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Oberholtzer, Family of Dr. E. E., 1945-1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Open University, 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Open University, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Operation Breadbasket, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Optometry-Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Optometry Building Groundbreaking, May 10, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Optometry, 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
  - Optometry, College of, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Orientation, 1961-1969 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Organization of University of Houston (Proposed Plan), 1937-1957 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Organization of University of Houston (Proposed Plan), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Packing Plant, Correspondence to, 1944-1956 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Panhellenic Building and Correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Parking Lots, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Parking Lots, 1972-1978 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Parking, Peripheral Lots (Brown and Root), 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Parking Recommendations - Spring, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Parking Regulations, 1974-1979 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Peace Corps, 1961-1967 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Services, 1972-1975 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Services, 1968-1979 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Peschke, Jerome M. - Assistant to the President 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Petroleum Engineering, Department of, 1955-1959 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Pharmacy Accreditation, 1956-1964 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Pharmacy Building-Texas Medical Center, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1952-1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1952-1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Philosophy of the University and Objectives, 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Photography Department Phasing Out, 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Physical Plant, 1962-1973 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Physics, Department of, 1964-1973 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Physics Department, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Placement Center, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Placement Center, 1975-1979 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Political Science - Doctor of Philosophy, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Post Office Department - Houston Division, 1969-1975 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - President, Duties of the, 1955-1958 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - President's Report U of H, 1955-1972 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - President's Report U of H, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - President's Scholars, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - President's Special Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Printing Plant and Graphics, 1964-1977 (Box 38, Folder 23-25)
  - Printing Plant and Graphics, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Programs, UH, to be Discontinued, undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Property, Adjacent to University of Houston, 1954-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Property, George Kelly, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Property Owned by UH at 3612 Parkwood, 1962-1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1968-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Public Administration, Master of, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Purser, Paul - Special Assistant to the President, 1968-1970 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
  - Registrar, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Religion Center Policy Board, 1965-1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Religious Activities, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Research Corporation, 1962-1974 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Research, Director of (and Office), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Research, Director of (and Office), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Research, Director of (and Office), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Research, Director of (and Office), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Research Grants, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Research Grants, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 18-19)
  - Research Grants, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 20-21)
  - Research Grants, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Rice Institute Associates, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Rice University, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Rice University - Racial Restriction Suit, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Rio Grande Regional Environmental Project, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Robertson, Mrs. Corbin J., 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Rockwell Endowment Fund, 1965-1973 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Rodeo, 1956-1965 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Roy Gustav Cullen Building, 1945-1961 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Roy Gustav Cullen Endowment Fund, 1950-1971 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Rules and Regulations - University of Houston, 1954-1960 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Russell Foundation, 1952-1959 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - San Jacinto College, 1963-1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Schlumberger House, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - SCONA, 1957-1969 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - SCUP Conference, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - SCUR, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Semi-centennial of the University of Houston, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Settegast Park and Settegast Family, 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Settegast Park and Settegast Family, 1958-1969 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Sharp, W. Harry, Vice Chancellor and Dean of Students, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Shell Companies Foundation, 1962-1978 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Shell Oil Company, 1962-1975 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Sigma Xi, 1959-1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Sigma Xi, 1964-1967 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Singleton, Roger S., Executive Vice President, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Singleton, Roger S., Executive Vice President, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Site - Correspondence, 1933-1941 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Site - Correspondence [Blueprints], 1933-1936 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Site - Dudley Tract Deed, 1939-1962 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Site - Landscaping, 1939-1945 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Site - Landscaping [Requisitions], 1937-1938 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Site - Right-of-way Deeds, 1936-1938 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Site - Sewer, 1937-1938 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Site - Sewer, 1939-1949 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Site - Streets, 1936-1940 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Skiles Act, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Preston, 1968-1969 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Preston, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Preston, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Smith, R. E. (Bob), 1952-1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Sobkowiak, Krystyna, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences, College of (Box 41, Folder 8-14)
    - General, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Geography, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Human Development and Consumer Sciences, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Military Science, Department of, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Military Science, Department of, UH ROTC Institution Scholarship Board, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Department of Political Science, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Department of Psychology, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Social Security, 1954-1968 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1968-1970 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1956-1974 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Solar Energy, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Solar Energy, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 21-23)
  - Solar Energy, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Solar Energy Laboratory, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Sororities, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - South Texas College (Junior), 1955-1974 (Box 41, Folder 27-28)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1961-1973 (Box 41, Folder 29-30)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Visitation, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Visitation, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Southern Association of Schools and Colleges, 1972-1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Southern Association Second Follow up Report, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Southern Association Trustees and Staff, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Southern Association Visitation Committee Report, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1954-1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Southern Regional Education, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
  - Southern University Conference, 1968-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14-15)
  - Southern University Conference, 1973-1980 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Speakers, 1956-1973 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Speakers - Jane Fonda, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Speakers - Rudd and Haile Cases, 1969-1972 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Speech, Department of, 1972-1974 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Speech Department, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Spencer, Tom, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - St. Thomas, University of, 1963-1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Staff Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Staff Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Staff Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Staff Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Staff Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Staff Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
  - Staff Legal Counsel, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Staff Meeting-Third Annual, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Staff Meeting-Fourth Annual, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Staff Meeting-Fifth Annual, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Staff Meeting-Sixth Annual, May 27, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Staff Meeting-Seventh Annual, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Staff Recognition Program, 1974-1978 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Staff - UH Employees, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - State Support - Bill Establishing, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - State Support, Hearing, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - State Support, Letters of Appreciation, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - State Support, Miscellaneous, 1960-1966 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - State Support, Municipal Study, 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - State Support Study, Other Universities, 1955-1962 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - State Support - Taxation, Study of, 1957-1960 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Stationary Requisitions, 1961-1972 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Streets, Development of, 1948-1950 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Student Association, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 27)